

JUEL HOSSAIN

WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

(3) +8801314882624

Juelhossainnn@gmail.com

Mirpur, Dhaka, Bangladesh

Portfolio Github

Linkedin

SKILLS

FRONT-END

HTML

CSS

JAVASCRIPT

TAILWIND CSS

REACT JS

REDUX

FIREBASE

BACK-END

MONGODB

MONGOOSE

EXPRESS JS

NODE JS

JASON WEB TOKEN

ABOUT

Hi, Welcome to my CV. My name is Juel Hossain. I am 23 years old. I am from, Dhaka, Bangladesh. I am a husband, A Javascript Programmer, designer, web developer and An Automation Engneer. I am Open To Work and Willing to Relocate.

EDUCATIONS

Primary School

2005 - 2009

Panpara Govt. Primary School

5 Years To complete. The grade was first class.

Junior School

2010-2012

Babupur Kasimuddin Bidyapith

3 Years To Complete. My grade was GPA 3.21 out of 5

Electric Engineering.

2013-2013

Rajbari Govt. Technical School and college

This was a four years course but I dropped out after six months.

Secondary School

2014-2016

Hammadia High School, Nayabazar, Dhaka

2.3 years to complete, the Subject was business study, and my grade was GPA 4.61 out of 5

Higher Secondary School

2016-2018

Government Bangla College Mirpur, Dhaka

2 years to complete, 1st year completed, The subject was business dropped out from 2nd year

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Recommendation Letter From LWS
- Certificates From Hacker Rank

SKILLS DESIGN PHOTOSHOP ILLUSTRATOR IN-DESIGN PRIEMIER PRO FIGMA TESTING WEB DRIVER IO APPIUM 2.0 POSTMAN JENKINS TOOLS LINUX GIT **VS CODE SOFT** RESEARCHING **TROUBLESHOOTING** TIME MANAGEMENT **LANGUAGES ENGLISH BANGLA** HINDI **HOBBIES** WATCHING MOVIES

PLAYING VIDEO GAMES

EXPERIENCES

Small Business

2018-2019

Cyber Cafe Shop Owner, Savar, Dhaka

After Dropping out of college, I started this business. This was a computer shop where people can rent computers for an hour for a little price.

Ride Sharing And Food Delivery

2019-2020

Uber, Pathao Itd and Shohoz Itd.

The business didn't go well so I started Ride Sharing with Uberand instant Parcel delivery with Pathao Ltd. When COVID-19 came ride-sharing was totally off. Then I started delivering food with pathao and shohoz Itd.

Graphic Designer

2020-2021

www.freelancer.com

After Learning adobe photoshop and adobe illustrator, I started freelancing. I made lots of brand identities and joined lots of contests here.

COURSES

Computer World

2020

Master of Graphic Design

Six months course covered adobe photoshop, illustrator, premiere pro, ms excel, ms word, how to freelance, and more.

Udemy.com

2022

Web Driver IO And Linux

the online course covered webdriver Io with appium 2.0 and Linux. I have done a total of three courses in udemy and got certified. after that, I learned postman from YouTube.

Programming Hero

2022

Complete Web Development Course

The course mentor was Jhankar Mahbub. Covered HTML, CSS, Javascript, Tailwind CSS, React Js, Node Js, Express Js, MongoDB, Firebase, JWT, Payment System and more.

Learn With Sumit

2022

Think In A Redux Way

The course mentor was Sumit Saha. The co-founder of analyzen Bangladesh ltd. Covered VanillaRedux, Redux Thunk, Redux Toolkit, Rtk Query, and more.